Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09; 9594
  - Photo Unit #: E0053 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Trench, North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938; 10322 (Item 11-0071)
  - Photo Unit #: E0056 [Two soldiers with their shoes off], undated; 10321 (Item 11-1422)
  - Photo Unit #: E0057 Brigade marching out of Seguro after being relieved, Feb 1938; 10320 (Item 11-0072)
  - Photo Unit #: E0061 After marching out of Seguro de Los Baños after being relieved, Feb 1938; 10319 (Item 11-1423)
  - Photo Unit #: E0065 Transmiciones [Transmissions] at Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 10318 (Item 11-1424)
  - Photo Unit #: E0066 [Soldiers, group], undated; 10317 (Item 11-1425)
  - Photo Unit #: E0070 [Soldiers, fortification], undated; 10316 (Item 11-1426)
  - Photo Unit #: E0073 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic at observation post at Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 10315 (Item 11-1427)
  - Photo Unit #: E0075 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 10314 (Item 11-1428)
  - Photo Unit #: E0076 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, [dead soldier], Feb 1938; 10313 (Item 11-1429)
  - Photo Unit #: E0077 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, [carrying body], Feb 1938; 10312 (Item 11-1430)
  - Photo Unit #: E0079 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, [carrying wounded man], Feb 1938; 10311 (Item 11-1431)
  - Photo Unit #: E0082 Max Bowers, chauffeur, [and ?], undated; 10310 (Item 11-1432)
  - Photo Unit #: E0083 Teniente Steve Tsermengas and autos at Hijar, Mar 1938; 10309 (Item 11-1433)
  - Photo Unit #: E0089 Retreat from Hijar to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10308 (Item 11-1434)
  - Photo Unit #: E0091 Retreat from Hijar to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10307 (Item 11-0073)
  - Photo Unit #: E0092 Runners organized for retreat through mountains to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10306 (Item 11-1435)
  - Photo Unit #: E0094 Resting while retreat to Caspe is organized, Mar 1938; 10305 (Item 11-1436)
  - Photo Unit #: E0096 MacKenzie-Papineau or Lincoln-Washington Battalion organized for march to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10304 (Item 11-1437)
  - Photo Unit #: E0097 MacKenzie-Papineau or Lincoln-Washington Battalion organized for march to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10303 (Item 11-1438)
  - Photo Unit #: E0098 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10302 (Item 11-1439)
  - Photo Unit #: E0100 Cavalry patrol on march to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10301 (Item 11-1440)
  - Photo Unit #: E0101 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10300 (Item 11-1441)
  - Photo Unit #: E0103 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10299 (Item 11-1442)
  - Photo Unit #: E0104 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10298 (Item 11-1443)
  - Photo Unit #: E0106 A rest during march to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10297 (Item 11-0074)
  - Photo Unit #: E0107 A drink of water during the march to Caspe, Mar 1938; 10296 (Item 11-1444)
  - Photo Unit #: E0111 Brigade Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10295 (Item 11-1445)
  - Photo Unit #: E0112 Brigade Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10294 (Item 11-0075)
  - Photo Unit #: E0113 Repairing a motor at 15th International Brigade garage, Mar 1938; 10293 (Item 11-1446)
  - Photo Unit #: E0114 Brigade Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10292 (Item 11-1447)
  - Photo Unit #: E0116 Auto Park kitchen at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10291 (Item 11-1448)
  - Photo Unit #: E0117 Joseph North at Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10290 (Item 11-1449)
  - Photo Unit #: E0118 Joseph North at Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10289 (Item 11-1450)
  - Photo Unit #: E0119 Civilians building refugios, Mora de Ebro, Mar 1938; 10288 (Item 11-1452)
  - Photo Unit #: E0121 Evacuation of civilians, Mora de Ebro, Mar 1938; 10287 (Item 11-1453)
  - Photo Unit #: E0122 Evacuation of civilians, Mora de Ebro, Mar 1938; 10286 (Item 11-1454)
  - Photo Unit #: E0123 Sound Truck at British Battalion at Batea, Mar 1938; 10285 (Item 11-0264)
  - Photo Unit #: E0124 Sound Truck at British Battalion at Batea [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Mar 1938; 369380 (Item 11-1898)
  - Photo Unit #: E0140 Major Robert Merriman, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Batea, Mar 1938; 10284 (Item 11-0265)
  - Photo Unit #: E0147 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938; 10283 (Item 11-0076)
  - Photo Unit #: E0148 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at munitions factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938; 10282 (Item 11-1455)
  - Photo Unit #: E0149 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938; 10281 (Item 11-1456)
  - Photo Unit #: E0151 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938; 10280 (Item 11-1457)
  - Photo Unit #: E0153 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938; 10279 (Item 11-1458)
  - Photo Unit #: E0155 A Barcelona street, Apr 1938; 10278 (Item 11-1459)
  - Photo Unit #: E0156 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion canteen, Ebro Front, Apr 1938; 10277 (Item 11-1850)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/57)
  - Photo Unit #: E0164 Popular Front Delegation and 15th International Brigade soldiers, Falset, Apr 14, 1938; 10276 (Item 11-0266)
  - Photo Unit #: E0166 Boys of "Pioneers" at 15th International Brigade, Falset, Apr 14, 1938; 10275 (Item 11-0267)
  - Photo Unit #: E0169 Popular front delegation at MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front [group under a tree; man holding a newspaper talks to several women], Apr 14, 1938; 10274 (Item 11-1460)
  - Photo Unit #: E0170 Wall newspaper and Popular Front delegations at MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front, Apr 1938; 10273 (Item 11-1828)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/3)
  - Photo Unit #: E0171 Popular front delegation at MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front [group in front of bulletin board], Apr 14, 1938; 10272 (Item 11-1461)
  - Photo Unit #: E0172 John Gates and MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front, Apr 14, 1938; 10271 (Item 11-0268)
  - Photo Unit #: E0176 Delegates of Popular Front from nearby village speaking at celebration in MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Apr 1938; 10270 (Item 11-1851)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/62)
  - Photo Unit #: E0178 Frank Rogers speaking at festival, Ebro Front, Apr 14, 1938; 10269 (Item 11-1462)
  - Photo Unit #: E0179 Frank Migone, José María Varela, John Rossen, and [?], Ebro Front, Apr 1938; 10268 (Item 11-0269)
  - Photo Unit #: E0182 [Soldiers distributing mail], undated; 10267 (Item 11-1463)
  - Photo Unit #: E0183 [Soldiers with mail], undated; 10266 (Item 11-1464)
  - Photo Unit #: E0184 [Soldiers with mail], undated; 10265 (Item 11-1465)
  - Photo Unit #: E0189 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Jack Cooper in foreground, Valverde, Feb 1938; 10264 (Item 11-1466)
  - Photo Unit #: E0191 Ruins, Feb 1938; 10263 (Item 11-1467)
  - Photo Unit #: E0200 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Batea [troops sitting on ground], Mar 1938; 10262 (Item 11-1468)
  - Photo Unit #: E0205 Staff compiling records, MacKenzie-Papineau, Batea, Mar 1938; 10261 (Item 11-0270)
  - Photo Unit #: E0212 Brigade Sanidad [Health] School, Mar 1938; 10260 (Item 11-0271)
  - Photo Unit #: E0213 Frank Dorsey and Frank Migoni Flores, Comisariado [Commissariat], Batea, Mar 1938; 10259 (Item 11-0272)
  - Photo Unit #: E0218 David Doran awarding citation for merit, undated; 10258 (Item 11-1469)
  - Photo Unit #: E0219 Presentation of award to Steve Tsermengas, Mar 1938; 10257 (Item 11-0273)
  - Photo Unit #: E0221 Burt Jackson, Thomas Page, Joseph Taylor, Mar 1938; 10256 (Item 11-0274)
  - Photo Unit #: E0222 Comrades building fortifications, Mar 1938; 10255 (Item 11-0275)
  - Photo Unit #: E0225 A chabola [shelter], Mar 1938; 10254 (Item 11-0276)
  - Photo Unit #: E0228 Stretcher-bearer class, Mar 1938; 10253 (Item 11-0277)
  - Photo Unit #: E0229 Eluard Luchell McDaniels, Batea, Mar 1938; 10252 (Item 11-0278)
  - Photo Unit #: E0232 Observers and Mappers School, Mar 1938; 10251 (Item 11-0279)
  - Photo Unit #: E0233 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938; 10250 (Item 11-0280)
  - Photo Unit #: E0234 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938; 10249 (Item 11-0281)
  - Photo Unit #: E0235 [Soldiers, relaxing/reading newspapers], Mar 1938; 10248 (Item 11-0282)
  - Photo Unit #: E0236 [Soldiers, relaxing/reading newspapers], Mar 1938; 10247 (Item 11-0283)
  - Photo Unit #: E0237 [Soldier, reading newspaper], Mar 1938; 10246 (Item 11-0284)
  - Photo Unit #: E0238 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938; 10245 (Item 11-0285)
  - Photo Unit #: E0240 Minuto on Motorcycle, Mar 1938; 10244 (Item 11-0286)
  - Photo Unit #: E0241 Joseph Brandt, Juan Mena, Mar 1938; 10243 (Item 11-0287)
  - Photo Unit #: E0243 Sound track, Batea, Mar 1938; 10242 (Item 11-0288)
  - Photo Unit #: E0244 [(?) addressing the troops], Mar 1938; 10241 (Item 11-0289)
  - Photo Unit #: E0245 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938; 10240 (Item 11-0290)
  - Photo Unit #: E0246 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938; 10239 (Item 11-0291)
  - Photo Unit #: E0247 Machine-gunners building nests, Batea, Mar 1938; 10238 (Item 11-0292)
  - Photo Unit #: E0248 William Susman [alias Bill Ellis], Joseph Brandt, Ivan Rujevcic, Juan Mena, Mar 1938; 10237 (Item 11-0293)
  - Photo Unit #: E0249 William Susman [alias Bill Ellis], Joseph Brandt, Ivan Rujevcic, Juan Mena, Mar 1938; 10236 (Item 11-0294)
  - Photo Unit #: E0250 Joseph Taylor and Burt Jackson, Mar 1938; 10235 (Item 11-0295)
  - Photo Unit #: E0254 Youth delegates address MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Mar 1938; 10234 (Item 11-0296)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative; Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/60)
  - Photo Unit #: E0255 [Soldier at attention], Mar 1938; 10233 (Item 11-0297)
  - Photo Unit #: E0256 [Soldiers at attention], Mar 1938; 10232 (Item 11-0298)
  - Photo Unit #: E0258 Trade Union Delegation in April, Apr 1938; 10231 (Item 11-0299)
  - Photo Unit #: E0260 [Soldiers, relaxing/smoking], Mar 1938; 10230 (Item 11-0300)
  - Photo Unit #: E0261 [Soldiers, relaxing at fortification], Mar 1938; 10229 (Item 11-0301)
  - Photo Unit #: E0264 Lieutenant Edwin Bee and topography class, Batea, Mar 1938; 10228 (Item 11-0302)
  - Photo Unit #: E0272 First-aid class, Sanidad [Health], undated; 10227 (Item 11-1470)
  - Photo Unit #: E0273 Dr. Mark Straus and Dr. Imek Bernstein, Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938; 10226 (Item 11-0263)
  - Photo Unit #: E0279 Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10225 (Item 11-0303)
  - Photo Unit #: E0281 Transmiciones [Transmissions], Apr 1938; 10224 (Item 11-0304)
  - Photo Unit #: E0282 John Gates, [?] and Milton Wolff, undated; 10223 (Item 11-1199)
  - Photo Unit #: E0283 Vladimir Copic, David Doran, Apr 1938; 10222 (Item 11-0305)
  - Photo Unit #: E0284 Group of soldiers [?], Apr 1938; 10221 (Item 11-0306)
  - Photo Unit #: E0285 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938; 10220 (Item 11-0307)
  - Photo Unit #: E0286 [Loading a truck], Apr 1938; 10219 (Item 11-0308)
  - Photo Unit #: E0287 [Loading a truck], Apr 1938; 10218 (Item 11-0309)
  - Photo Unit #: E0288 [Loading a truck], Apr 1938; 10217 (Item 11-0310)
  - Photo Unit #: E0291 [Digging/building fortifications (?)], Apr 1938; 10216 (Item 11-0311)
  - Photo Unit #: E0292 [Digging/building fortifications (?)], Apr 1938; 10215 (Item 11-0312)
  - Photo Unit #: E0293 [Soldiers, marching], Apr 1938; 10214 (Item 11-0313)
  - Photo Unit #: E0294 Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10213 (Item 11-0314)
  - Photo Unit #: E0296 Dressing a wound, Sanidad [Health], undated; 10212 (Item 11-1471)
  - Photo Unit #: E0297 Lou Ziven, Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10211 (Item 11-0315)
  - Photo Unit #: E0298 Dr. Imek Bernstein, Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10210 (Item 11-0316)
  - Photo Unit #: E0299 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic and [?], Apr 1938; 10209 (Item 11-0317)
  - Photo Unit #: E0302 Saul Wellman, Apr 1938; 10208 (Item 11-0318)
  - Photo Unit #: E0305 Cubans, Apr 1938; 10207 (Item 11-0319)
  - Photo Unit #: E0307 Washing Up, Apr 1938; 10206 (Item 11-0320)
  - Photo Unit #: E0308 [14th International Brigade (?)], Apr 1938; 10205 (Item 11-0321)
  - Photo Unit #: E0309 [14th International Brigade (?)], Apr 1938; 10204 (Item 11-0322)
  - Photo Unit #: E0310 [(?) addressing the troops], Apr 1938; 10203 (Item 11-0323)
  - Photo Unit #: E0311 [(?) addressing the troops], Apr 1938; 10202 (Item 11-0324)
  - Photo Unit #: E0312 [Three Spanish (?) soldiers], Apr 1938; 10201 (Item 11-0325)
  - Photo Unit #: E0314 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Corbera, Apr 1938; 10200 (Item 11-0326)
  - Photo Unit #: E0317 Going to the Botaja front, Apr 1938; 10199 (Item 11-0327)
  - Photo Unit #: E0320 Going to the Botaja front, Apr 1938; 10198 (Item 11-0328)
  - Photo Unit #: E0325 Captain [?], Ivan Rujevcic, Lieutenant Steve Tsermengas, Apr 1938; 10197 (Item 11-0329)
  - Photo Unit #: E0326 Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10196 (Item 11-0330)
  - Photo Unit #: E0328 [Kitchen/cooking; man holding a ladle over a pot of soup], undated; 10195 (Item 11-1472)
  - Photo Unit #: E0330 Action Shots: Batea, Gandesa, Apr 1938; 10194 (Item 11-0331)
  - Photo Unit #: E0333 Some of our tanks at Batea during Fascist offensive, undated; 10193 (Item 11-1473)
  - Photo Unit #: E0336 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938; 10192 (Item 11-1200)
  - Photo Unit #: E0340 Action Shots: Batea, Gandesa, Apr 1938; 10191 (Item 11-0332)
  - Photo Unit #: E0344 Action Shots: Batea, Gandesa, Apr 1938; 10190 (Item 11-0333)
  - Photo Unit #: E0345 Soldiers watching Fascist planes, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938; 10189 (Item 11-1474)
  - Photo Unit #: E0347 Miguel Lausurica of Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938; 10188 (Item 11-1475)
  - Photo Unit #: E0348 Group from Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938; 10187 (Item 11-1476)
  - Photo Unit #: E0349 Oficina comrades at Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938; 10186 (Item 11-1477)
  - Photo Unit #: E0351 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa, Apr 1938; 10185 (Item 11-1478)
  - Photo Unit #: E0357 Group in Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938; 10184 (Item 11-1479)
  - Photo Unit #: E0358 Auto Park kitchen serves lunch, Mora La Nueva, Apr 1938; 10183 (Item 11-0077)
  - Photo Unit #: E0361 Armory at work, Mas Roig, Mar 1938; 10182 (Item 11-1480)
  - Photo Unit #: E0364 Comrades of Pagaduria and Intendencia, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10181 (Item 11-1481)
  - Photo Unit #: E0365 Unidentified Soldier in Chair, 304906 (Item 11-1875)
  - Photo Unit #: E0367 Highway near Mora La Nueva during retreat from Gandesa, Apr 1938; 10180 (Item 11-0078)
  - Photo Unit #: E0368 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa, Apr 1938; 10179 (Item 11-1482)
  - Photo Unit #: E0369 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa [with cart and flock of sheep], Mar 1938; 10178 (Item 11-1483)
  - Photo Unit #: E0370 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa [mules under a tree], Mar 1938; 10177 (Item 11-1484)
  - Photo Unit #: E0371 Commissariat wall newspaper, Falset, Apr 1938; 10176 (Item 11-1485)
  - Photo Unit #: E0372 Auto Park machine shop, Alcover, Apr 1938; 10175 (Item 11-1486)
  - Photo Unit #: E0376 British Battalion, Darmos [cook serving men], Apr 1938; 10174 (Item 11-1487)
  - Photo Unit #: E0377 [?] and Louis Secundy of Auto Park at Mora La Nueva, Mar 1938; 10173 (Item 11-0079)
  - Photo Unit #: E0378 Auto Park kitchen serves lunch, Mar 1938; 10172 (Item 11-0080)
  - Photo Unit #: E0381 Lunch time in the Auto Park, Mar 1938; 10171 (Item 11-0081)
  - Photo Unit #: E0382 Lunch time in the Auto Park, Mar 1938; 10170 (Item 11-0082)
  - Photo Unit #: E0383 Louis Secundy, [?], [?], Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10169 (Item 11-1488)
  - Photo Unit #: E0384 Group from the Auto Park, Mar 1938; 10168 (Item 11-0083)
  - Photo Unit #: E0385 Group from the Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938; 10167 (Item 11-1489)
  - Photo Unit #: E0387 Frank Arvola, chief cook in Auto Park, Alcover, Apr 1938; 10166 (Item 11-0334)
  - Photo Unit #: E0388 Lieutenant [?] Sanchez, Commissar Samuel Gonshak, Lieutenant Louis Secundy, Alcover, Apr 1938; 10165 (Item 11-0335)
  - Photo Unit #: E0392 Godfrey Thompson cleaning rifle, Brigade Armory, Falset, Apr 1938; 10164 (Item 11-1201)
  - Photo Unit #: E0398 ? talking to James Bourne, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10163 (Item 11-0336)
  - Photo Unit #: E0399 Samuel Gonshak and Solomon Rosenblum [alias Sol Rose], Apr 1938; 10162 (Item 11-0380)
  - Photo Unit #: E0402 Coffee at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10161 (Item 11-0337)
  - Photo Unit #: E0403 Brigade staff meeting, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10160 (Item 11-1490)
  - Photo Unit #: E0404 Brigade Office, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10159 (Item 11-0338)
  - Photo Unit #: E0406 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10158 (Item 11-0339)
  - Photo Unit #: E0408 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic confers with staff officers, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10157 (Item 11-0340)
  - Photo Unit #: E0412 James Bourne and Captain Carl Slater, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10156 (Item 11-0341)
  - Photo Unit #: E0414 [Soldier relaxing, Darmos], Apr 1938; 10155 (Item 11-0342)
  - Photo Unit #: E0416 Brigade Staff meeting, Apr 1938; 10154 (Item 11-0343)
  - Photo Unit #: E0417 Brigade officers meeting, Darmos; Captain David Kami, commander of Sapodores [at right], Apr 1938; 10153 (Item 11-1491)
  - Photo Unit #: E0421 José María Varela, Daniel Pasternack [?], Eloy Bouha [?], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10152 (Item 11-0344)
  - Photo Unit #: E0422 Showers in the 15th International Brigade, Falset, Apr 1938; 10151 (Item 11-1492)
  - Photo Unit #: E0423 Engineers working on fortifications, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10150 (Item 11-0345)
  - Photo Unit #: E0427 Antonio Garcia, Auto Park, 59th Battalion Miguel Lausurica [?], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10149 (Item 11-0346)
  - Photo Unit #: E0434 [3 men] writing letters home, undated; 10148 (Item 11-1493)
  - Photo Unit #: E0435 Showers, 15th International Brigade, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10147 (Item 11-0347)
  - Photo Unit #: E0437 Letty Abraham of Bagdad, Mack Coad of Alabama, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10146 (Item 11-0348)
  - Photo Unit #: E0439 Letty Abraham of Bagdad, Mack Coad of Alabama, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10145 (Item 11-0349)
  - Photo Unit #: E0441 David (Red) Drummond, George Watt, William Maher, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10144 (Item 11-0350)
  - Photo Unit #: E0442 Commissars Meeting, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10143 (Item 11-0351)
  - Photo Unit #: E0443 John Weldon, Lincoln-Washington Secretary, and Felix Kuzman, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10142 (Item 11-0352)
  - Photo Unit #: E0445 Card game in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10141 (Item 11-0353)
  - Photo Unit #: E0446 Card game in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Apr 1938; 10140 (Item 11-1202)
  - Photo Unit #: E0447 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos; [soldiers resting one holding a map], Apr 1938; 10139 (Item 11-1494)
  - Photo Unit #: E0448 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion after April 2nd retreat, Darmos; [sitting on ground, drinking wine], Apr 1938; 10138 (Item 11-1495)
  - Photo Unit #: E0449 Joe Bianca, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10137 (Item 11-0354)
  - Photo Unit #: E0450 Joe Bianca,cleaning a rifle, and others, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10136 (Item 11-1496)
  - Photo Unit #: E0451 Card game in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10135 (Item 11-0355)
  - Photo Unit #: E0453 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10134 (Item 11-0356)
  - Photo Unit #: E0454 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10133 (Item 11-0357)
  - Photo Unit #: E0455 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10132 (Item 11-0358)
  - Photo Unit #: E0466 Commissariat wall board, Ebro Front, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10131 (Item 11-1497)
  - Photo Unit #: E0467 [Fortification, soldiers at attention], Apr 1938; 10130 (Item 11-0359)
  - Photo Unit #: E0468 [Soldiers with truck], Apr 1938; 10129 (Item 11-0360)
  - Photo Unit #: E0469 Auto Park group, Apr 1938; 10128 (Item 11-0361)
  - Photo Unit #: E0471 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938; 10127 (Item 11-0362)
  - Photo Unit #: E0476 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938; 10126 (Item 11-0363)
  - Photo Unit #: E0480 [Machine-gun nest (?)], Apr 1938; 10125 (Item 11-0364)
  - Photo Unit #: E0481 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938; 10124 (Item 11-0365)
  - Photo Unit #: E0482 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938; 10123 (Item 11-0366)
  - Photo Unit #: E0483 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10122 (Item 11-0367)
  - Photo Unit #: E0484 [Soldier in grass hut], Apr 1938; 10121 (Item 11-0368)
  - Photo Unit #: E0485 [Machine-gun crew], Apr 1938; 10120 (Item 11-0369)
  - Photo Unit #: E0486 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938; 10119 (Item 11-0370)
  - Photo Unit #: E0487 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938; 10118 (Item 11-0371)
  - Photo Unit #: E0488 Band concert, Apr 1938; 10117 (Item 11-0372)
  - Photo Unit #: E0490 Band concert, Apr 1938; 10116 (Item 11-0373)
  - Photo Unit #: E0491 15th International Brigade band, Mar 1938; 10115 (Item 11-1498)
  - Photo Unit #: E0496 Band concert, Apr 1938; 10114 (Item 11-0374)
  - Photo Unit #: E0498 Band concert, Apr 1938; 10113 (Item 11-0375)
  - Photo Unit #: E0501 Band concert, Apr 1938; 10112 (Item 11-0376)
  - Photo Unit #: E0505 Lincoln-Washington [officers?] and Estado Major, undated; 10111 (Item 11-1499)
  - Photo Unit #: E0506 Lincoln-Washington and Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 10110 (Item 11-1500)
  - Photo Unit #: E0507 Lincoln-Washington and Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated; 10109 (Item 11-1501)
  - Photo Unit #: E0510 [Soldiers, waiting to eat], undated; 10108 (Item 11-0377)
  - Photo Unit #: E0511 [Soldiers, relaxing], undated; 10107 (Item 11-0388)
  - Photo Unit #: E0512 [Preparing fortifications (?)], undated; 10106 (Item 11-0389)
  - Photo Unit #: E0513 [Automobile], undated; 10105 (Item 11-0390)
  - Photo Unit #: E0514 Battalion Commissars Robert Cooney, Antonio Gil Cabezas, Frank Rogers, J.M. Varseda, George Watt, Sandor Voros, 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938; 10104 (Item 11-0391)
  - Photo Unit #: E0515 Carl Syvanen, MacKenzie-Papineau, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10103 (Item 11-0392)
  - Photo Unit #: E0517 Max Farrar, cook, Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10102 (Item 11-0393)
  - Photo Unit #: E0521 Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10101 (Item 11-0394)
  - Photo Unit #: E0523 [Soldiers, eating/drinking], May 1938; 10100 (Item 11-0395)
  - Photo Unit #: E0525 Wall newspaper, Sanidad [Health], undated; 10099 (Item 11-0396)
  - Photo Unit #: E0526 Wall newspaper, undated; 10098 (Item 11-0397)
  - Photo Unit #: E0529 Dr. Imek Bernstein, Dr. Mark Straus, Alexander Goldberg, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10097 (Item 11-0398)
  - Photo Unit #: E0530 Murray Nemeroff and Alexander Goldberg, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10096 (Item 11-0399)
  - Photo Unit #: E0531 Murray Nemeroff and Alexander Goldberg, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938; 10095 (Item 11-0400)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/19)
  - Photo Unit #: E0532 Jose Martinez Fernandez [?] and Miguel Estella Angel, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10094 (Item 11-0401)
  - Photo Unit #: E0539 Antonio Gil Cabezas (Commissar, 59th Battalion), Captain German Hernandez (Commander, 59th Battalion), Captain Mark Millman (Adjuntant, 59th Battalion), Ebro Front, Apr 1938; 10093 (Item 11-1502)
  - Photo Unit #: E0544 Plano Mayor, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10092 (Item 11-0402)
  - Photo Unit #: E0545 Comrades in rain on railroad tracks, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10091 (Item 11-0403)
  - Photo Unit #: E0546 Battalion activities, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938; 10090 (Item 11-0404)